

DIAN MUSFIROH

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

PERSONAL PROFILE

Hard working and effective web developer who has more than 3 years of expertise. Bilingual, astute and deadline-driven. Seeking a developer position where a strong understanding of technology and a marketing background can be best utilised.

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

- Hands-on SQL experience
- JavaScript,MySQL Node.js, Docker, PHP and Python experience
- Web API experience
- · Working knowledge of typescript and golang
- Figma and Photoshop experience

WORK EXPERIENCE

BACK END DEVELOPER

KPT Klik Digital Teknologi | 2022 - Present

- Directs software design and development
- Contributed to back-end experience and collaborated on APIs.
- Developed and integrated payment processing features onto eCommerce websites.

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Render Printing Gorontalo | 2021 - 2022

· Worked with clients to define marketing and design vision for various graphic design projects.

JUNIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER INTERN smart data integrasi | 2020 - 2021

- Learnt and followed department processes to help develop software according to requirements.
- Modified existing software to correct errors and optimize efficiency
- Contributed to back-end experience and collaborated on APIs.

GET IN CONTACT

in linkedin.com/in/dian-musfiroh/

dianmusfiroh90@gmail.com Bachelor of Computer Science, Present

- **A** +62-8229-1786-044
- dianmusfiroh.site
- github.com/Dianmusfiroh
- @dianmusfiroh
- Gorontalo, Indonesia

EDUCATION HISTORY

UNIVERSITY OF ICHSAN

POLITEKNIK GORONTALO

Associate Degree of Informatics Engineering. 2010 **Honor Roll**

- · Member of the student association
- Member of the Program Team

OTHER SKILLS

- The ability to analyze complex technical information
- Can analyze, design and implement database structures
- Detail oriented
- Excellent problem solver